Last night,i watched a football match on TV between VietNam team and Thailand team
Vietnam team dressed in red, while Thailand team wore blue
After the refree signaled, the game was started.The game was exciting from the first minute
In the first half, our team didn't score any goals
In the second half, just 10 minutes later, Cong Vinh scored his first goal for Vietnam team
The whole stadium was very loud
The air was very noisy in the field. After that, Thailand team scored the 1-1 equalizer
The spectator of our team had a quite feeling lost but Van Quyen scored a goal to add more in a few minutes later
By the end of the game, there was no more goals was scored
The referee whistled to finish the match.Vietnam team won 2-1. This football match was really exciting